Welcome to SBI Insurance Portal
Tutorial,
we will see how to create a bike mud party on this link
or you
will open the link of this, first of all these details will be
filled in it, so first of all you have to enter these three
details and after that you have to
create the policy, one thing to keep in mind in this is that the
payment link is not sent in it, so
whoever makes the payment will download the
policy payment clear policy along with it on the portal,
let's get the
details,
enter Scorpio and click on Famous,
now this is a private car and two wheeler,
in this the root party of both can be created,
incarnate to read the party here only, hand
sweetu girl will click on third party,
we do not have to search by entering the number in it,
if we do this then the third
party option will not appear, we will do it in it and
click on don't know the and don't know vehicle number system,
which is the first option at the bottom and once it refreshes,
this one will appear, inside it we will enter the
registration number and fill all the details
and in this
we will cut the note on the previous policy details,
if you enter the details of the policy in it
without  The policy will also start from current
so try
not to enter VS Kochi in it, we will enter the registration plate in it
and tell me it is
21A,
see I had entered the bike details and
clicked on gate,
A victim is comprehensive, the biggest
problem in this will be tormenting the third party,
after clicking on it, this with owner
which we ask will show the mind,
if we want to remove the owner in this then we will
click on remove below, then that will be removed and
if we want to make both then we will
click on sisters, I am making this policy with owner, so
I will click on Siddha Yantra,
if you want to remove the co-owner
then we will click on remove also on that, so
see this has become 80, after removing it
I want to make both, so I will add
it on this and it has come bye, we will enter the engine number,
chassis number in it, so
next we will enter the customer details, we have entered the
name Mamta, we will add the sons, we will
click on maximum, after doing this the
work of making a single Asma payment  And all the rest of the
details will remain, the servicemen have entered the
scientific
loot
and tell me it has happened, you can
loot it, from
here you can enter the registration
details with the tax details and
see that the test is starting here, from which
date will it start or it will stop at you,
click on IS Accepted,
click on it, see here there
is an option to send any payment link, now
in this you have to directly make the payment by netting your debit card,
immediately after the payment the option of download PDF will come
or and you can